♪
- If he lands this,
如果他成功了，
I'll wear a grass skirt and dance the hula.
我就穿草裙跳草裙舞。
I never said coconut bra.
我可没说椰子壳胸罩。
- Eh, it would look weird without it.
呃，没有它看起来会很奇怪。
- You know, one of these days one of us is gonna beat you
你知道，总有一天我们中的一个会打败你
and put you in a coconut bra.
然后给你穿上椰子壳胸罩。
- Nobody puts Dicky in a coconut bra.
没人能把迪基放进椰子壳胸罩里。
- Hey, kids, we'd like you to meet someone.
嘿，孩子们，我们想让你们见个人。
- This is Simone. She's shopping with her Mom.
这是西蒙娜，她和妈妈一起购物。
all: Hey, Simone.
大家：嘿，Simone。
- Hello. Hey. Hi.
你好。嘿。嗨。
Aloha.
阿罗哈。
- Her family just moved here.
她家刚搬到这里。
She's about your age.
她大概和你同龄。
- She doesn't know anybody.
她谁也不认识。
- Don't rub it in her face, Dad.
别往她脸上贴金了，爸爸。
- Hang in there, kid. - Bye.
坚持住，孩子。 - 再见。
- Could you excuse us for a second, Simone?
你能暂时回避一下吗，Simone？
- Yeah. - Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
好的。 - 嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Can you kids not take a hint?
你们这些孩子就不能领会一下暗示吗？
- I don't know. Give us one.
- 我不知道。给我们一个。
- Imagine what it feels like for Simone.
- 想象一下Simone的感受。
Not knowing anyone here, not being included.
在这里谁也不认识，不被包括进去。
- Still waiting on that hint.
- 还在等那个暗示。
- Okay.
- 好吧。
- Mom, we get the hint.
- 妈妈，我们明白了。
- But we just like to choose our own friends.
- 但我们只是喜欢自己选择朋友。
Someone we have a strong emotional connection with.
和我们有强烈情感联系的人。
Or someone that can put Dicky in a coconut bra.
或者能帮Dicky穿上椰子壳胸罩的人。
- Not bad, Dicky. I still think you could use a little more hip.
- 不错，Dicky。我还是觉得你可以再多一点摇摆。
- I am so glad we're friends.
- 我真高兴我们是朋友。
- Me too. And if you like this,
- 我也是。如果你喜欢这个，
I can show you something even cooler at my house.
- 我可以在我家给你看更酷的东西。
- A tennis court? A soccer field?
- 网球场？足球场？
- And a science lab.
- 还有科学实验室。
- Simone, your house is amazing. - Thanks.
- Simone，你家真是太棒了。 - 谢谢。
- Who has a science lab in their house?
- 谁家里会有科学实验室？
- Yeah, are your parents inventors?
- 是啊，你父母是发明家吗？
- No, I am.
- 不，我是。
- Simone?
Simone?
- Great. We finally make a cool friend
太好了，我们终于交到了一个酷朋友，
and it turns out she's a ghost.
结果她是个鬼魂。
- I'm not a ghost.
我不是鬼魂。
I'm just wearing an invisibility suit.
我只是穿了一件隐形衣。
- There's no such thing as an invisibility suit.
不存在什么隐形衣。
- There wasn't. Until I invented it.
以前没有。直到我发明了它。
- [gasps]
（倒抽一口气）
all: Whoa.
哇。
- I'm not passing out because I'm scared.
- 我不是因为害怕而晕倒。
I'm passing out because it's so amazing.
我晕倒是因为这太神奇了。
- I'm passing out because I'm scared.
- 我晕倒是因为我害怕。
- I'm passing out because people passing out
- 我晕倒是因为看到别人晕倒
always makes me pass out.
总是让我也晕倒。
- [chuckles] Don't worry, I'm good.
- [轻笑] 别担心，我没事。
Okay, here I go.
好吧，我要开始了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
[upbeat music]
欢快的音乐
- A lot of people pass out when they see the floating head.
很多人看到漂浮的头就会晕倒。
The juice will help.
果汁会帮助你。
- That invisibility suit blew my mind.
那件隐形衣让我大吃一惊。
It's incredible.
真是不可思议。
- It's just a little something I've been toying around with.
这只是我一直在玩弄的小玩意儿。
I create high-tech fabrics and clothing for various uses.
我为各种用途创造高科技面料和服装。
- Ooh. What does that cardigan do?
哦，那件开衫有什么功能？
- Keeps me warm.
让我保持温暖。
- Genius.
天才。
- So what's your latest invention?
那么你最新的发明是什么？
- Oh. It's top secret.
哦，这是最高机密。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Hey, Carmichael, can you excuse us for a minute?
嘿，卡迈克尔，你能回避一下吗？
- Of course, Miss MacAfee.
当然可以，麦卡菲小姐。
- I've had secrets stolen before.
我以前有过秘密被窃取的经历。
You never know who you can trust.
你永远不知道你能信任谁。
So, can I trust you?
那么，我能信任你吗？
- Of course. Right, guys? - Yeah, we're trustworthy. - Yeah. - Yeah.
- 当然可以。对吧，伙计们？ - 是的，我们值得信赖。 - 是的。 - 是的。
- Okay. Then to the Terrace of Trust.
- 好的。那么去信任之台。
- Ooh, awesome. - Yes!
- 哦，太棒了。 - 是的！
- [claps] - Whoa.
- [鼓掌] - 哇。
Purple is a trustworthy color.
紫色是一种值得信赖的颜色。
- Now, if you could have any super power, what would it be?
- 现在，如果你能拥有任何超能力，那会是什么？
- Flying. - X-ray vision.
- 飞行。 - 透视眼。
- Time travel. - Dancing.
- 时间旅行。 - 跳舞。
- What if I told you I'm really close to completing a suit
如果我告诉你，我即将完成一套服装，
that enables you to do all four?
能让你拥有所有这四种能力呢？
all: Whoa, cool.
所有人: 哇，太酷了。
- Except the first three.
4: 除了前三种。
- Even cooler.
5: 更酷了。
- It makes even the worst dancer the best dancer
6: 它能让最差的舞者变成最好的舞者，
I should have it ready by Saturday.
7: 我应该能在周六前准备好。
If you're around, you can try it then.
8: 如果你有空的话，到时候可以试试。
- That sounds perfect for Dawn. She's a terrible dancer.
9: 这对Dawn来说太完美了。她跳舞很糟糕。
Go ahead, Dawn, show her.
10: 去吧，Dawn，给她展示一下。
For science.
为了科学。
- [sighs] Come on, Dawn. Show me how you dance.
来吧，Dawn，给我展示一下你是怎么跳舞的。
We're friends.
我们是朋友。
- I think both friendship and science
我认为在这种情况下，友谊和科学都会失败。
would lose in this situation.
Dawn，听着，
- [sighs] Dawn, look,
既然我们在信任的露台上，
since we're on the Terrace of Trust,
我就告诉你一个秘密。
I'll let you in on a secret.
这件衣服的灵感来源是我自己。
My inspiration for this suit was me.
等等，真的吗？
- Wait, really? - Watch.
看着。
[dance music playing]
♪ ♪
- You think that's bad? [exhales sharply]
你觉得那很糟糕吗？
[dance music playing]
♪ ♪
- It's the Terrace of Terror.
这里是恐怖露台。
- The world needs that suit.
世界需要那套服装。
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，嘿 哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- Wow, Simone sounds amazing.
哇，Simone听起来很棒。
What kind of things does she invent?
她发明了些什么？
- I can't talk about it. Top secret.
- 我不能谈论这个。绝密。
- Well, we're family. I gave birth to you.
- 好吧，我们是家人。我生了你。
- Tom, screaming and crying in the waiting room is not giving birth.
- 汤姆，在等候室里尖叫和哭泣并不算生孩子。
- All I know is when I was done, I had four children.
- 我只知道当我完成时，我有四个孩子。
- Well, speaking of things your father didn't deliver,
- 嗯，说到你父亲没送来的东西，
a gentleman named Carmichael just dropped this off.
- 一个叫卡迈克尔的先生刚送来了这个。
kids: Cool.
孩子们: 酷。
- Hey, Harpers. kids: Whoa.
- 嘿，哈珀一家。
- I had a great time with you guys today
- 我今天和你们玩得很开心
and I want to invite Nicky, Ricky, and Dawn
- 我想邀请尼基、里基和道恩
to come over tomorrow and hang out.
明天来我家玩吧。
kids: Yes! - Wait a minute.
太好了！等等。
She didn't invite me.
她没邀请我。
- Why do you still sound excited?
那你为什么还这么兴奋？
- I don't know. I'm very confused right now.
我不知道，我现在很困惑。
- She obviously meant to invite me
她显然是想邀请我，
and not the three of you.
而不是你们三个。
Yes!
太好了！
- Honey, that's not what Simone said.
亲爱的，Simone不是这么说的。
- That's okay.
没关系。
It's not like you guys are gonna go without me.
你们不会不带我去的，对吧？
- [whistling softly]
- [轻轻吹口哨]
- Are you really gonna go?
- 你真的要去吗？
- Come on. You'd go without us.
- 得了吧，你会不带我们去。
- Of course I would.
- 当然会的。
But that's the way it should be.
但事情就该这样。
- I'm sorry. I know you guys are quads,
- 对不起，我知道你们是四胞胎，
but you can't expect to be included in everything
但你不能期望每件事都和你兄弟姐妹一样。
your brothers and sister are.
- 这说不通。
- This doesn't make any sense.
- 这没有意义。
Well, maybe I heard it wrong.
好吧，也许我听错了。
- Just to be clear, Dicky is not invited.
为了澄清，迪基没有被邀请。
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- These hoodies are so comfy.
这些连帽衫真舒服。
- I call those the Hoodie-Do. - Why?
我把那些叫做改头换面连帽衫。- 为什么？
- Because those hoodies give you a new do.
因为那些连帽衫能给你换个新发型。把你们的帽子摘下来。
Take your hoods off.
哇。- 不可思议。
- Wow. - Incredible.
希望没邀请迪基不会尴尬。
- I hope it's not awkward that I didn't invite Dicky.
不会。- 一点也不。
- Nope. - Not at all.
他喜欢自己的头发保持原样。
- He loves his hair the way it is.
- 他喜欢他的头发现在的样子。
- Cool. Because I have a bunch
- 太好了，因为我还有一堆
of other great stuff to show you.
其他很棒的东西要给你看。
- I feel guilty. Dicky was right.
- 我觉得内疚。Dicky说得对。
We really shouldn't have come without him.
我们真的不应该没有他就来。
Let's just go. both: Yeah.
我们走吧。
- Hey, guys, do you want a ride in my invisi-blimp?
两人: 嗯。
all: Yeah!
- 嘿，伙计们，想坐我的隐形飞艇吗？
[upbeat music]
所有人: 嗯！
- [laughing] - Oh, hey, Dicky.
- [笑] - 哦，嘿，Dicky。
- What's up, dude? - Hey, you.
- 最近怎么样，伙计？ - 嘿，你。
- What's up with the scarves?
- 围巾是怎么回事？
- Dicky, what are you doing with my books?
- 迪基，你拿我的书干嘛？
- Reading them. [laughter]
- 在读它们。[笑声]
- "Reading them." No, I mean seriously.
- “在读它们。”不，我是说认真的。
- Yeah. - Seriously.
- 是啊。 - 认真的。
Being away from you all,
离开你们大家之后，
I realized something.
我意识到了一些事情。
You're kinda holding me back.
你们有点拖我后腿了。
Anyway, did you guys have a fun time with Simone?
话说，你们和西蒙娜玩得开心吗？
- Yeah, no big deal. - Just hung out.
- 是的，没什么大不了的。 - 只是出去玩了。
- Guys, you don't have to pretend.
- 伙计们，你们不必假装。
you didn't have an awesome time.
你们并没有玩得很开心。
I'm totally cool that you have a separate friend.
我完全没问题，你们有个别的朋友。
- Good 'cause we had a great time.
- 那就好，因为我们玩得很开心。
- So much fun. - She has an invisi-blimp.
- 非常有趣。 - 她有个隐形飞艇。
- Still doesn't explain the scarves.
- 这还是解释不了那些围巾。
- Oh, that was to protect our Hoodie-do hairdos
- 哦，那是为了保护我们的连帽衫发型
from the invisi-wind.
免受隐形风的侵袭。
- All right. [doorbell rings]
- 好吧。 [门铃响]
- From Miss MacAfee.
来自麦菲小姐。
- Thanks, Carmichael.
谢谢，卡迈克尔。
Hey, we got another cube.
嘿，我们又多了一个立方体。
Oh, uh, sorry, Dicky.
哦，呃，对不起，迪基。
- Carry on.
继续。
- I have to say, Dicky, I'm really proud of you
迪基，我得说，我真为你感到骄傲
for not freaking out over being excluded.
没有因为被排除在外而慌张。
- Hey, it's me, Simone.
嘿，是我，西蒙妮。
I want to invite Nicky and Ricky to come over tomorrow.
我想邀请尼基和瑞奇明天过来。
Hope you two can make it.
希望你们俩能来。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. [chuckles] Nicky and Ricky?
哇，哇，哇，哇。[轻笑] Nicky和Ricky？
There's got to be a glitch in the hologram.
这一定是全息影像出了问题。
- I want to invite Nicky and Ricky...
- 我想邀请Nicky和Ricky...
- And Dawn. - To come over tomorrow.
- 还有Dawn。 - 明天过来。
- See? [chuckles]
- 看吧？[轻笑]
I was invited.
我被邀请了。
- Dawn, Dawn, Dawn.
- Dawn, Dawn, Dawn。
Chapter four has a wonderful section
第四章有一个很棒的部分
on rejection and denial.
关于拒绝和否认。
- I just don't understand.
- 我就是不明白。
- Oh, I know some of the words are big,
哦，我知道有些词很大，
but if you just sound them out,
但如果你只是把它们读出来，
you'll be okay.
你会没事的。
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Almost there.
快到了。
- Do you feel guilty about Dawn and Dicky not being here?
你对Dawn和Dicky不在这里感到内疚吗？
- I would, but I'm too focused on what she's concocting.
我会的，但我太专注于她在策划什么了。
- Here you go. A hot fudge sundae.
给你。一个热巧克力圣代。
- Where?
哪里？
- Right here.
both: Whoa!
- Dig in, boys. - Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Hey, guys. [chuckles]
Sorry I'm late. Ooh, sundae time.
- Dawn?
I didn't expect you today.
I only invited Ricky and Nicky.
- And Dawn!
See? You even said my name right now.
看？你刚才还正确地叫了我的名字。
- Dawn, that was you.
- 晨曦，那是你。
- Fine. Just why wasn't I invited back?
- 好吧。那为什么我没有被再次邀请呢？
I thought we got along.
我以为我们相处得不错。
- Join me on the Terrace of Trust.
- 跟我来，到信任的露台上。
- Ooh. Good things happen up there.
- 哦。好事总在那儿发生。
I'm going up!
我要上去了！
[claps]
（鼓掌）
[squeals]
（尖叫）
- Look, I know this whole thing must be very confusing for you.
- 听着，我知道这一切对你来说一定很困惑。
But while you're here, I do have a little something
但既然你在这里，我确实有点关于星期六的事情
to tell you about Saturday.
要告诉你。
Sit. - Ooh.
坐下。
The big day. I'm all ears.
哦。
- First, can you swim? - Like a fish.
大日子。我洗耳恭听。
Okay, now just tell me about Saturday.
首先，你会游泳吗？
- You're not gonna be there.
像鱼一样。
- Ahh!
好的，现在就告诉我关于星期六的事。
But why did you care if I can--
你不会在那里。
[water splashes]
啊！
Oh, got it.
哦，明白了。
- Just to be clear, I don't swim.
- 说清楚，我不游泳。
- [exhales sharply] Eat, eat.
- [深呼吸] 吃，吃。
- Okay.
- 好的。
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- I don't get it. Why didn't Simone want me there?
- 我不明白。为什么Simone不希望我在那里？
I mean, I'm likable, right?
我是说，我讨人喜欢，对吧？
- Definitely. - I'm nice.
- 当然。 - 我人很好。
- The nicest. - I am a joy to be around.
- 最好的人。 - 我是个让人愉快的人。
- Look, we just need to get your mind off of this.
- 看，我们只是需要让你不再想这件事。
Find something else for you to do.
找点别的事情让你做。
Like learn a new language.
比如学一门新语言。
- Where is the nearest bus station?
- 最近的公交站在哪里？
"Waar is de dichtstbijzijnde bushalte?"
最近的公交站在哪里？
- Okay, I don't get it. I an freaking out
- 好吧，我不明白。我因为被拒绝而抓狂，
over being rejected, and you're reading
而你却在看书和学新语言。
and learning a new language.
你是怎么做到的？
How do you do it?
- 我不确定。
- Ik weet het niet zeker.
- 好吧，你需要停下来
- Okay, you need to stop that
在我不确定之前。
before I ik weet your niet zeker.
在我知道之前，我不确定。
- What's got her all boos en verbittered?
她为什么这么生气和苦涩？
- I should go.
我应该走了。
- Hey, Dawn.
嘿，Dawn。
Sorry about earlier, but we brought you an ice cream sundae.
抱歉刚才的事，但我们给你带了个冰淇淋圣代。
- Wow, aren't you generous?
哇，你真是慷慨啊？
One little bite.
就一小口。
both: No! Duck!
不行！快躲！
[splatters]
[溅射声]
- This is so unfair!
这太不公平了！
I should have been the one bringing you guys
我本应该带你们去
tiny exploding ice cream sundaes.
吃小爆炸冰淇淋圣代。
- Dawn, it's like Mom said,
- 小霞，就像妈妈说的，
you have to get used to us all not having the same friends.
你得习惯我们大家不是都有同样的朋友。
- Okay, well, if I were you, I wouldn't get too comfortable
- 好吧，如果我是你，我不会太自在
because one of you is gone next.
因为你们中的一个很快就会离开。
- [scoffs] - That's not true.
- [嗤之以鼻] - 那不是真的。
- Simone loves us. - Yeah.
- 西蒙娜爱我们。 - 是的。
- I don't know. I see a pattern.
- 我不知道。我看到了一个模式。
- [scoffs] There's no pattern. [doorbell rings]
- [嗤之以鼻] 没有模式。[门铃响]
- Huh. That happened yesterday.
嗯，昨天也发生了同样的事。
It has all the makings of a pattern.
这完全符合一个模式的特征。
Oh, hello, Carmichael. Pattern.
哦，你好，卡迈克尔。模式。
Do you have something for us?
你有什么要给我们的吗？
- Indeed I do.
确实有。
- Thank you. Pattern.
谢谢。模式。
- Hi, about Saturday,
嗨，关于星期六，
I'm so excited about a breakthrough I just had
我太兴奋了，因为我刚刚有了一个突破，
that I can't wait till then.
我等不到那时候了。
I want to show it to you today.
我想今天就把这个展示给你看。
So, Ricky... - Yes!
所以, Ricky... - 是的!
- Rhymes with Nicky, who's the only one I'm inviting.
- 和Nicky押韵, 他是唯一我邀请的人。
- Yes! - No!
- 是的! - 不!
- Pattern!
- I gotta go get my dancing shoes.
- 我得去拿我的舞鞋。
- Uh, before I go,
- 呃, 在我走之前,
Simone's new invention is pretty cool, huh?
Simone的新发明很酷, 对吧?
- Wait, she told you about it.
- 等等, 她告诉你了。
- Yeah. It's the, you know, thing.
- 是的。就是那个, 你知道的, 东西。
The other thing and the other other thing.
另一个东西和另一个另一个东西。
What was it that she called it?
她是怎么称呼它的？
It's right on the tip of my tongue.
就在我嘴边，但就是想不起来。
- Well, it's going to have to stay there
- 好吧，那就让它留在那里吧
because we know nothing about any of those things.
因为我们对那些东西一无所知。
Or the other things.
或者是其他的东西。
- Yeah. And even if we did know,
- 是的。即使我们真的知道，
we wouldn't tell you, Carmichael.
我们也不会告诉你的，卡迈克尔。
- Oh, I'll tell you what it is.
- 哦，我来告诉你那是什么。
It's dat zijn uw zaken niet, butler gast.
那不关你的事，管家先生。
- Right. That's what I thought it was.
- 对。我也是这么想的。
- Dicky, we weren't supposed to tell him.
Dicky，我们不应该告诉他的。
What if he translates that?
如果他翻译了那句话怎么办？
- Then he'll find out I said her invention is,
那他就会知道我说她的发明是，
"None of your business, butler dude."
“不关你的事，管家老兄。”
- Wait, that was weird.
等等，这有点奇怪。
Why would Carmichael want to know what Simone's invention is?
为什么Carmichael想知道Simone的发明是什么？
- Maybe he wants to steal her idea.
也许他想偷她的主意。
- I mean, she did say someone stole her ideas in the past.
我是说，她确实说过过去有人偷过她的主意。
- The butler did it!
是管家干的！
- That's what we're saying, Dicky.
我们说的就是这个，Dicky。
- No. I just finished this mystery novel.
不，我刚读完这本侦探小说。
"The Butler Did It."
《管家干的》。
I did not see that coming.
我真没料到。
- [whistling]
[吹口哨]
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
- If Carmichael's the one who's been stealing Simone's ideas,
如果卡迈克尔是那个一直在偷西蒙妮点子的人，
we have to tell Nicky.
我们得告诉尼基。
- Ah, well, I'm off to test the you-know-what.
啊，好吧，我要去测试那个你知道的东西了。
Oh, I'll give you a hint.
哦，我给你个提示。
[whispers] It's the dance suit.
[低语] 是那件舞蹈服。
- Nicky, there's something we have to tell you.
Nicky, 我们有件事必须告诉你。
- We think the butler's about to steal Simone's idea.
我们认为管家即将偷走Simone的创意。
- Carmichael? He's a mensch.
Carmichael？他是个正直的人。
- That's Yiddish for a person of integrity and honor.
那是意第绪语，指一个有诚信和荣誉感的人。
- Hey, don't you want to protect your friend Simone?
嘿，难道你不想保护你的朋友Simone吗？
- Oh, I see. You're all just jealous.
哦，我明白了。你们都只是嫉妒。
I don't have time for this.
我没时间处理这个。
I must dance.
我必须去跳舞。
- If Nicky's not going to tell Simone, we have to.
如果Nicky不打算告诉Simone，我们必须这么做。
- Why would we want to help her?
我们为什么要帮她？
She obviously doesn't care about us.
她显然不在乎我们。
- But you heard what Mom said.
- 但你听到了妈妈说的话。
How would we feel if we were Simone?
如果我们是Simone，我们会怎么想？
Would you want your idea stolen
你是希望你的想法被偷走，
or would you want someone to warn you?
还是希望有人警告你？
- [sighs] Fine.
- [叹气] 好吧。
Dicky, you coming?
Dicky，你来吗？
- Nah. I just started a new mystery novel.
- 不了。我刚开始了本新的侦探小说。
- "The Butler Did It."
- 《管家干的》。
- Oh, man. Again?
- 哦，天哪。又是这个？
- The butler always does it.
- 管家总是干的。
That's why they're called "The Butler Did It Mysteries."
这就是为什么它们被称为“管家干的悬疑小说”。
- You can judge a book by its cover.
- 你可以从封面判断一本书。
♪
- Clear. Carmichael's nowhere in sight.
- 清楚了。卡迈克尔不见踪影。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Did I do it better than him?
- 我做得比他好吗？
- Sadly, yes.
- 可悲的是，是的。
- Okay, so what do we do now?
- 好吧，我们现在该怎么办？
- Well, since Nicky won't back us up
那么，既然妮基不肯在我们告诉卡迈克尔的事情上支持我们
when we tell her about Carmichael,
我们就得躲起来，直到能找到单独对付西蒙的机会
we're just gonna need to hide until we can get Simone alone.
我们要躲哪儿？- 我有办法！
- Where are we gonna hide? - I got it!
我们就藏在隐形衣里吧！
Let's just hide in the invisibility suits.
好极了！
- Yes! - Sweet!
我隐形了吗？- 没有，我呢？
- Am I invisible? - No. Am I?
没有，我也看不见你们俩
- No. - I can't see either of you.
迪基，转过身来。
- Dicky, turn around.
哦。
- Oh.
这些不是正确的套装
- These aren't the right suits.
这些不是合适的西装。
- Ooohh, someone's coming.
哦，有人来了。
- So, ready to try out my dance suit?
那么，准备好试试我的舞蹈服了吗？
I have to say, it's way better than my last invention:
我得说，这比我的上一个发明好多了：
emotion-activated safety suits that inflate like airbags.
情绪激活的安全服，像安全气囊一样膨胀。
They were a total fail.
它们完全失败了。
They're right...
他们是对的……
Huh, I could have sworn I hung them right there.
嗯，我敢肯定我把它们挂在那儿了。
- Did you hear that? These are airbag suits
你听到了吗？这些是气囊服
and they're motion-activated, so don't move anything.
而且是运动激活的，所以不要动任何东西。
- They were supposed to be activated by fear,
- 它们应该是由恐惧激活的，
like before an accident, but they're over-sensitive
就像事故发生前那样，但它们过于敏感
and any emotion sets them off.
任何情绪都会触发它们。
- She didn't say motion-activated.
- 她没说运动激活。
She said emotion-activated.
她说的是情绪激活。
- Then don't feel anything.
- 那就不要有任何感觉。
- But you sound angry. - I'm not angry!
- 但你听起来很生气。 - 我没有生气！
- So, ready to dance?
- 那么，准备好跳舞了吗？
- Well, I-I thought I was,
- 嗯，我以为我准备好了，
but now that I think about it,
但现在想想，
I'm not so sure. - What? Why?
我不太确定。 - 什么？为什么？
- Well, your stuff's cool and all,
嗯，你的东西很酷，
but it just doesn't feel right without my brothers and sister.
但没有我的兄弟姐妹在身边，感觉就不对。
- Sorry, but I just got this feeling I couldn't trust them.
对不起，但我就是有种感觉，我不能信任他们。
- Couldn't trust them?
不能信任他们？
They kept your secret the whole time.
他们可是一直帮你保守秘密的。
Ricky, Dicky, and Dawn are the most honorable
瑞奇、迪基和道恩是我认识的最值得尊敬
and trustworthy people I know.
和可信赖的人。
- Aww.
哦。
- I feel weird inside.
我心里感觉怪怪的。
- Uh-oh. Emotions!
- 哎呀，情绪来了！
[suits inflating]
[服装充气中]
- What are you doing here?
- 你们在这里做什么？
- We came to warn you that Carmichael's the one
- 我们来警告你，卡迈克尔是那个一直在偷你发明的人。
who's been stealing your inventions.
- 现在他还想偷你的舞蹈服创意。
- And now he's trying to steal your dance suit idea too.
- 他试图从我们这里套话，但我告诉他，
- He tried to get it out of us, but I told him,
"这不关你的事，管家老兄。"
"Dat zijn uw zaken niet, butler gast."
- 你告诉他这是，"不关你的事，管家老兄"？
- You told him it was, "None of your business, butler dude"?
- 你会说荷兰语？
- You speak Dutch?
- 不会。我们一直在关注你。
- No. We've been keeping an eye on you.
- 不，我们一直在留意你。
- We?
- 我们？
- Yes, we.
- 是的，我们。
Carmichael? - Hello.
卡迈克尔？ - 你好。
Or as Dicky might say in Dutch, hallo.
或者用迪基的荷兰语说，你好。
- Carmichael's not actually a butler dude.
- 卡迈克尔实际上不是个管家哥们。
He's my father dude.
他是我老爸哥们。
- So the butler didn't do it.
- 所以管家没干这事。
- Congratulations.
- 恭喜。
The last few days have been a test
过去几天是个考验
and you guys passed with flying colors.
你们表现得非常出色。
- What? - What do you mean?
- 什么？ - 你什么意思？
- A test? - Colors can fly?
- 测试？ - 颜色能飞？
- And he's back.
- 他回来了。
- In the past, kids I've hung out with
- 过去，和我一起玩的孩子们
have really let me down.
真的让我失望了。
So I was looking for trustworthy friends.
所以我一直在寻找值得信赖的朋友。
People who are going to keep my secrets.
那些会保守我秘密的人。
- About your inventions?
- 关于你的发明？
- About anything. Like how I'm secretly afraid of cats.
- 关于任何事情。比如我其实很怕猫。
Or what boy I have a crush on.
或者我对哪个男孩有好感。
- [gasps]
- [惊讶声]
Is it me?
是我吗？
You can tell me.
你可以告诉我。
It'll be our secret.
这将成为我们的秘密。
I think she has a crush on me.
我觉得她对我有好感。
- So this whole thing was a test?
- 所以这一切都是个测试？
- Yes. And you passed. You guys can be my friends.
- 是的。你通过了。你们可以成为我的朋友。
- Well, we're not sure if you can be ours.
- 不过，我们还不确定你是否能成为我们的朋友。
- What do you mean?
- 你这是什么意思？
- Look, Simone, we like you.
- 听着，Simone，我们喜欢你。
It's just testing your friends is just weird.
只是测试你的朋友这种事很奇怪。
- Yeah. That's not what friends do.
- 是的。这不是朋友该做的事。
- You may be a genius,
- 你可能是个天才，
but you're not too smart when it comes to people.
但在人际关系方面你不太聪明。
- I told her the test was a dumb idea.
- 我告诉过她这个测试是个愚蠢的主意。
- Dad!
- 爸爸！
Look, I'm sorry, guys.
听着，我很抱歉，伙计们。
I just really like hanging out with you.
我只是真的很喜欢和你们一起玩。
Can you give me a second chance?
你们能给我一个第二次机会吗？
- Quaddle up.
- 准备好了。
Skip the Quaddle.
跳过准备。
[exhales sharply]
[急促呼气]
Excuse me.
对不起。
We'll give you a second chance,
我们会给你第二次机会，
but you have to promise
但你得保证
no more weird tests. - Got it.
不再做奇怪的测试。 - 明白了。
- Oh, and there's one other thing.
- 哦，还有一件事。
We need to borrow the invisibility suits
我们需要借用隐形衣
for something. - What?
做点事情。 - 什么？
- Ha-ha!
哈哈！
[exhales sharply]
[急促呼气]
Ahh! Anne, we have another ghost!
啊！安妮，我们又遇到鬼了！
- Good one, guys. - Hey, there's Mae.
——干得好，伙计们。——嘿，梅在那儿。
Mae, over here!
梅，这边！
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 是的！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 是的！ ♪